(Bernadette:)...he's putting a lot of pressure on me
to get a prenup.
- Ouch!
- Yeah.
(Bernadette:)- Howie's gonna freak out.
- Parental pressure can be daunting.
(Amy:)I remember the battle with my mother
about shaving my legs.
(Amy:)Last year, I finally gave in
and let her do it.
(Bernadette:)I just don't know
how I'm gonna break it to him.
I'm a believer in breaking bad news
to a guy when you're in bed.
(Penny:)That's how I told my high school
boyfriend I slept with his brother.
(Penny:)That's how I told his brother
the same thing.
(Bernadette:)I don't know.
I don't wanna manipulate him with sex.
(Penny:)Oh, sweetie, that's what sex is for.
(Amy:)The connection between marriage
and money is nothing new.
The term "wed" referred
to the money and livestock...
(Amy:)...the groom paid the bride's father.
(Amy:)For example, you're adorable,
intelligent and a good earner.
(Amy:)I could conservatively see you going
for at least two oxen and a goose.
(Amy:)You would fetch a unicorn.